<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-27T23:48:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Richard’s jekkyl/Ge</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Cranes</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cranes" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cranes" /><published>2019-11-25T21:33:36-07:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T21:33:36-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cranes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cranes">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T-Zy0VI4lws&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T-Zy0VI4lws/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Roof Video&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A roof is the top covering of a building, including all materials and constructions necessary to support it on the walls of the building or on uprights; it provides protection against rain, snow, sunlight, extremes of temperature, and wind.[1] A roof is part of the building envelope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The characteristics of a roof are dependent upon the purpose of the building that it covers, the available roofing materials and the local traditions of construction and wider concepts of architectural design and practice and may also be governed by local or national legislation. In most countries a roof protects primarily against rain. A verandah may be roofed with material that protects against sunlight but admits the other elements. The roof of a garden conservatory protects plants from cold, wind, and rain, but admits light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A roof may also provide additional living space, for example a roof garden.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Excavators</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/excavators" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Excavators" /><published>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/excavators</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/excavators">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T-Zy0VI4lws&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T-Zy0VI4lws/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Roof Video&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A basement or cellar is one or more floors of a building that are completely or partly below the ground floor.[1] It generally is used as a utility space for a building, where such items as the boiler, water heater, breaker panel or fuse box, car park, and air-conditioning system are located; so also are amenities such as the electrical distribution system and cable television distribution point. In cities with high property prices, such as London, basements are often fitted out to a high standard and used as living space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In British English, the word basement is used for underground floors of, for example, department stores, but the word is only used with houses when the space below the ground floor is habitable, with windows and (usually) its own access. The word cellar applies to the whole underground level or to any large underground room. A subcellar is a cellar that lies further underneath.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Finishers</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/finishers" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Finishers" /><published>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/finishers</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/finishers">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BZBU-TBQ13M&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BZBU-TBQ13M/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;IMAGE ALT TEXT HERE&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Power trowels differ in the way they are controlled:
Ride-on power trowels are used by an operator sitting on a seat upon the machinery, controlling the power trowel with the necessary buttons.
Walk-behind power trowels are used by an operator walking behind the machine.
A hand tool for the same task is called a concrete float.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Spray Foam</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/foam" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spray Foam" /><published>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/foam</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/foam">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H6jiGKOSABo&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H6jiGKOSABo/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Open Cell Vs Closed Cell&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spray foam is a chemical product created by two materials, isocyanate and polyol resin, which react when mixed with each other and expand up to 30-60 times its liquid volume after it is sprayed in place. This expansion makes it useful as a specialty packing material which forms to the shape of the product being packaged and produces a high thermal insulating value with virtually no air infiltration.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Iron</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/iron" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Iron" /><published>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/iron</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/iron">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PorCp4mslcI&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PorCp4mslcI/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Structural Steel Installation&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A structural/ornamental ironworker fabricates and erects (or even dismantles) the structural steel framework of pre-engineered metal buildings, single and multi-story buildings, stadiums, arenas, hospitals, towers, wind turbines, and bridges.[1] [2] Ironworkers also unload, place and tie reinforcing steel bars, (rebar) as well as install post-tensioning systems, both of which give strength to the concrete used in piers, footings, slabs, buildings, and bridges. Ironworkers load, unload, place, and set machinery and equipment as well as operate power hoists, forklifts, and aerial lifts. They unload, place, and fasten metal decking, safety netting, and edge rails to facilitate safe working practices. Ironworkers finish buildings by erecting curtain wall and window wall systems, stairs and handrails, metal doors, and sheeting and elevator fronts. Ironworkers perform all types of industrial maintenance as well.[3]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically ironworkers mainly worked with wrought iron or cast iron, but today they utilize many different materials including ferrous and non-ferrous metals, plastics, glass, concrete, and composites.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kitchens</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/kitchens" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kitchens" /><published>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/kitchens</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/kitchens">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FCFwKlbjGhw&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FCFwKlbjGhw/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Millwork&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Woodworking is the activity or skill of making items from wood, and includes cabinet making (cabinetry and furniture), wood carving, joinery, carpentry, and woodturning.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Richard from Page</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sips</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sips" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sips" /><published>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sips</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sips">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tqfEVrY09SA&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tqfEVrY09SA/0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sips Bandsaw&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Structural insulated panels (SIPs) are a high performance building system for residential and light commercial construction. The panels consist of an insulating foam core sandwiched between two structural facings, typically oriented strand board (OSB).  SIPs are manufactured under factory controlled conditions and can be fabricated to fit nearly any building design. The result is a building system that is extremely strong, energy efficient and cost effective. Building with SIPs will save you time, money and labor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>